<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Flax &amp;amp; Teal</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Flax &amp;amp; Teal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© {year} Flax &amp; Teal Limited.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 14:10:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flaxandteal.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Flax &amp;amp; Teal Limited respects your privacy and is committed to protecting any personal information you share with us. This policy explains what information we collect, how we use it, and your rights under the UK General Data Protection Regulation (UK GDPR).
Information We Collect We do not actively collect personal data unless you choose to provide it to us via our Contact Us form or in any other type of communication e.</description></item><item><title>Technology</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/technology/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/technology/</guid><description>Open source is pervasive throughout IT, especially within cloud, data and web. While all sectors are now indirectly dependent on open source projects, uptake has been far slower outside IT, at least outside major international innovation hubs.
We believe this is due to a traditional view of IP and technology business value, that is being superseded, driven by the realisable net business benefit to procuring open source solutions in all sectors, and proven case studies in AI, cloud, automation, IoT and automotive.</description></item><item><title>Terms and Conditions</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/terms-and-condition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/terms-and-condition/</guid><description>Introduction Welcome to Flax and Teal&amp;rsquo;s website. By accessing or using our website, you agree to comply with and be bound by these Terms and Conditions. Please read them carefully. If you do not agree with any part of these terms, you must not use our website. These Terms and Conditions, along with our Privacy Policy, govern your use of our website and services.
Use of the Website You agree to use our website only for lawful purposes and in a way that does not infringe the rights of, restrict, or inhibit anyone else&amp;rsquo;s use and enjoyment of the website.</description></item><item><title>Thank you 🙏</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/thank-you/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/thank-you/</guid><description>Our support team will reach out to you shortly. Return Home</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/maritime-mile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/maritime-mile/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DTFF Application Support | Flax &amp; Teal Northern Ireland</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/dtff/dtff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/dtff/dtff/</guid><description>DTFF Application Support – Northern Ireland The Digital Transformation Flexible Fund (DTFF) offers Northern Ireland SMEs between £5,000 and £20,000 to invest in advanced digital technologies such as AI, data, and process automation. But competition is intense, and funding calls close quickly. A small mistake or weak alignment with DTFF criteria can mean losing out.
At Flax &amp;amp; Teal, we provide specialist DTFF application support to help you strengthen, refine, or fully manage your submission.</description></item></channel></rss>