<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Flax &amp;amp; Teal</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Flax &amp;amp; Teal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 14:10:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flaxandteal.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arches for Science</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/arches-science/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/arches-science/</guid><description>Arches for Science We have deployed, and are currently hosting, Arches as a data repository for a large- scale international cross-disciplinary research project on urban policy.
This involved interviewing a range of researchers, from social scientists to geologists, to establish a common base of requirements, and ensuring UKRI (UK Research and Innovation) compliant documentation and data management.</description></item><item><title>Arches Work</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/arches-work/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/arches-work/</guid><description>About Arches Arches is an open source data management platform which makes it possible for meaningful organisational change. Jointly funded by the World Monument Fund and the Getty Conservation Institute, it has evolved into a powerful asset management and GIS tool. We have conducted Arches workshops with the Arches team to build a roadmap for integrating the Arches software with modern DevOps flows, and are the leading team in doing so.</description></item><item><title>Arches for Heritage</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/arches-heritage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/arches-heritage/</guid><description>Arches for Cultural Heritage Institutions We are currently in the process of delivering a long-term digital transformation project for Northern Irish public sector, migrating all of their current and historic heritage- based data to a customised Arches HER (Historic Environment Record) instance. They required a secure and accessible database capable of holding more than 200,000 records safely and without data loss.
This has involved site visits, workshops and detailed data modelling exercises, and has been supported on the technology side by Kubernetes, Python-in-the-cloud, Ray data workflows and deployed to GKE.</description></item><item><title>Maritime Mile</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/maritime-mile/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/maritime-mile/</guid><description>Explore Belfast’s Maritime Mile History Like Never Before Welcome to the Virtual Heritage Experience Dive into the past with an innovative way to explore historical images, videos, audio clips, and captivating stories from heritage archives. Our project uses 3D/VR technology to bring history to life right at your fingertips.
How it Works:
Scan &amp; Discover: Find one of our 6 strategically placed QR code plaques, scan it with your smartphone, and step into a snapshot of history.</description></item><item><title>Our Products</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/projects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/projects/</guid><description>Product &amp;amp; Project Work Full Project | Lead Partner | Consortium Member Flax &amp;amp; Teal has prepared, run and participated in a number of projects - some as part of internal or consortium product-building, some facilitating clients.
Our full-scale projects involve designers, media &amp;amp; communications specialists, developers, app &amp;amp; mobile technologists, infrastructure engineers, analysts and data scientists, as required.
This is a selection of our public R&amp;amp;D work. If you have specific questions about our private experience in a specific area, such as data gathering, IoT or training, please contact us directly at info@flaxandteal.</description></item><item><title>Our Clients</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/clients/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/clients/</guid><description>Testimonials Deloitte Flax &amp;amp; Teal partnered with Deloitte to build an enterprise-level data gathering Human Resources platform. The digital transformation project changed the way resources are managed by quantifying time allocated to various departments. This project involved an iterative Agile, full stack build and development of cloud infrastructure. The team deployed Kubernetes to ensure flexibility and resilience of service.
Boards123 Boards123 innovates Board Performance. We do this with our software, services and training products.</description></item><item><title>Our Services</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/services/</guid><description>Services Coding | Cloud Architecture | Consulting Flax &amp;amp; Teal is a consultancy focused on openly-licensed technologies, serving public and private sector through web-based products and services in computational engineering, geospatial analysis and data science (machine learning and AI).
Flax &amp;amp; Teal builds tools for private and public sector including publicly-shared, reusable parts - these are often web platforms providing behind-the-scenes analysis of open data, geography and physics.
F&amp;amp;T is also part of a multidisciplinary consortium of small businesses in Northern Ireland: Avata Industries, which together build openly-licensed products.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/about/</guid><description>About Us Where it all began Our name, Flax &amp;amp; Teal has an interesting back story, which broadly summarises our company&amp;rsquo;s philosophy. Our Director, Phil Weir, spent over 3 years completing his PhD in New Zealand, a whopping 11,468 miles from his roots in Northern Ireland. Turns out, Northern Ireland and New Zealand have more in common than one would think.
_Flax_ is a flowering plant which grows natively both in NI and NZ, whereas _Teal_ is a species of duck (no, really), which is also natively found in both regions.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/contact/</guid><description>Contact us Contact us via email on info@flaxandteal.co.uk to find out more.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/team/</guid><description>Meet the team From an initial team of one in Belfast in 2013, Flax and Teal has expanded significantly since, adding people in new locations and expanding our capabilities to meet growing customer needs.
Now spread across 4 locations, Northern Ireland, Bulgaria, India and California, the Flax and Teal team currently consists of 13 people and continues to grow.
With customers across Ireland, the UK, Europe and Northern America the team spans across several timezones.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/testimonials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/testimonials/</guid><description>Case Studies We&amp;rsquo;ve been fortunate enough to work with a wide range of clients across various sectors, ensuring project completion and client satisfaction along the way.
Arches A selection of our commercial Arches work, an open source data management solution.
Deloitte Flax &amp;amp; Teal partnered with Deloitte to build an enterprise-level data gathering Human Resources platform. The digital transformation project changed the way resources are managed by quantifying time allocated to various departments.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/video/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/video/</guid><description>Hong Kong FinTech Week Hong Kong FinTech Week video. Browser does not support embedded videos.</description></item></channel></rss>