<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Flax &amp;amp; Teal</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Flax &amp;amp; Teal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 10:41:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Our Products</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/projects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/projects/</guid><description>Product &amp;amp; Project Work Full Project | Lead Partner | Consortium Member Flax &amp;amp; Teal has prepared, run and participated in a number of projects - some as part of internal or consortium product-building, some facilitating clients.
Our full-scale projects involve designers, media &amp;amp; communications specialists, developers, app &amp;amp; mobile technologists, infrastructure engineers, analysts and data scientists, as required.
This is a selection of our public R&amp;amp;D work. If you have specific questions about our private experience in a specific area, such as data gathering, IoT or training, please contact us directly at info@flaxandteal.</description></item><item><title>Our Clients</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/clients/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/clients/</guid><description>Testimonials Deloitte Flax &amp;amp; Teal partnered with Deloitte to build an enterprise-level data gathering Human Resources platform. The digital transformation project changed the way resources are managed by quantifying time allocated to various departments. This project involved an iterative Agile, full stack build and development of cloud infrastructure. The team deployed Kubernetes to ensure flexibility and resilience of service.
Boards123 Boards123 innovates Board Performance. We do this with our software, services and training products.</description></item><item><title>Our Services</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/services/</guid><description>Services Coding | Cloud Architecture | Consulting Flax &amp;amp; Teal is a consultancy focused on openly-licensed technologies, serving public and private sector through web-based products and services in computational engineering, geospatial analysis and data science.
Flax &amp;amp; Teal builds tools for private and public sector including publicly-shared, reusable parts - these are often web platforms providing behind-the-scenes analysis of open data, geography and physics.
F&amp;amp;T is also part of a multidisciplinary consortium of small businesses in Northern Ireland: Avata Industries, which together build openly-licensed products.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/contact/</guid><description>Contact us Contact us via email on info@flaxandteal.co.uk to find out more.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/team/</guid><description>Meet the team! We have steadily grown our team from 2013 until now, as we continue to expand in Belfast and beyond. We have clients from the UK, Europe and more, and our team base has grown to reflect this.
Phil Weir | Founder Founder and director of Flax &amp;amp; Teal Ltd., Phil is also lead architect on our projects and services, as an experienced scientist and web developer. Phil has a PhD in Python-based mathematical simulation, and is one of Northern Ireland&amp;rsquo;s qualified Kubernetes trainer.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/testimonials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/testimonials/</guid><description>Testimonials Deloitte Flax &amp;amp; Teal partnered with Deloitte to build an enterprise-level data gathering Human Resources platform. The digital transformation project changed the way resources are managed by quantifying time allocated to various departments. This project involved an iterative Agile, full stack build and development of cloud infrastructure. The team deployed Kubernetes to ensure flexibility and resilience of service.
Boards123 Boards123 innovates Board Performance. We do this with our software, services and training products.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/video/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/video/</guid><description>Hong Kong FinTech Week Hong Kong FinTech Week video. Browser does not support embedded videos.</description></item></channel></rss>