<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Flax &amp;amp; Teal</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Flax &amp;amp; Teal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 10:41:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Our Products</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/projects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/projects/</guid><description>Product &amp;amp; Project Work Full Project | Lead Partner | Consortium Member Flax &amp;amp; Teal has prepared, run and participated in a number of projects - some as part of internal or consortium product-building, some facilitating clients.
Our full-scale projects involve designers, media &amp;amp; communications specialists, developers, app &amp;amp; mobile technologists, infrastructure engineers, analysts and data scientists, as required.
This is a selection of our public R&amp;amp;D work. If you have specific questions about our private experience in a specific area, such as data gathering, IoT or training, please contact us directly at info@flaxandteal.</description></item><item><title>Our Clients</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/clients/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/clients/</guid><description>Testimonials Deloitte Flax &amp;amp; Teal partnered with Deloitte to build an enterprise-level data gathering Human Resources platform. The digital transformation project changed the way resources are managed by quantifying time allocated to various departments. This project involved an iterative Agile, full stack build and development of cloud infrastructure. The team deployed Kubernetes to ensure flexibility and resilience of service.
Boards123 Boards123 innovates Board Performance. We do this with our software, services and training products.</description></item><item><title>Our Services</title><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/services/</guid><description>Services Coding | Cloud Architecture | Consulting Flax &amp;amp; Teal is a consultancy focused on openly-licensed technologies, serving public and private sector through web-based products and services in computational engineering, geospatial analysis and data science (machine learning and AI).
Flax &amp;amp; Teal builds tools for private and public sector including publicly-shared, reusable parts - these are often web platforms providing behind-the-scenes analysis of open data, geography and physics.
F&amp;amp;T is also part of a multidisciplinary consortium of small businesses in Northern Ireland: Avata Industries, which together build openly-licensed products.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/about/</guid><description>About Us Where it all began Our name, Flax &amp;amp; Teal has an interesting back story, which broadly summarises our company&amp;rsquo;s philosophy. Our Director, Phil Weir, spent over 3 years completing his PhD in New Zealand, a whopping 11,468 miles from his roots in Northern Ireland. Turns out, Northern Ireland and New Zealand have more in common than one would think.
_Flax_ is a flowering plant which grows natively both in NI and NZ, whereas _Teal_ is a species of duck (no, really), which is also natively found in both regions.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/contact/</guid><description>Contact us Contact us via email on info@flaxandteal.co.uk to find out more.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/team/</guid><description>Meet the team From an initial team of one in Belfast in 2013, Flax and Teal has expanded significantly since, adding people in new locations and expanding our capabilities to meet growing customer needs.
Now spread across 4 locations, Northern Ireland, Bulgaria, India and California, the Flax and Teal team currently consists of 13 people and continues to grow.
With customers across Ireland, the UK, Europe and Northern America the team spans across several timezones.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/testimonials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/testimonials/</guid><description>Testimonials Deloitte Flax &amp;amp; Teal partnered with Deloitte to build an enterprise-level data gathering Human Resources platform. The digital transformation project changed the way resources are managed by quantifying time allocated to various departments. This project involved an iterative Agile, full stack build and development of cloud infrastructure. The team deployed Kubernetes to ensure flexibility and resilience of service.
Boards123 Boards123 innovates Board Performance. We do this with our software, services and training products.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/video/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://flaxandteal.co.uk/pages/video/</guid><description>Hong Kong FinTech Week Hong Kong FinTech Week video. Browser does not support embedded videos.</description></item></channel></rss>